export default [
    {
        question: "meat",
        answer: "la viande",
        categColor: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "ham",
        answer: "le jambon",
        categColor: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "chicken",
        answer: "le poulet",
        categColor: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "fish",
        answer: "le poisson",
        categColor: "green"
    },
    {
        question: "banana",
        answer: "une banane",
        categColor: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "green-beans",
        answer: "des haricots verts",
        categColor: "purple"
    },
    {
        question: "peas",
        answer: "des petits pois",
        categColor: "purple"
    },
    {
        question: "potato",
        answer: "une pomme de terre",
        categColor: "purple"
    },
    {
        question: "mushroom",
        answer: "un champignon",
        categColor: "purple"
    },
    {
        question: "pear",
        answer: "une poire",
        categColor: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "onion",
        answer: "un oignon",
        categColor: "purple"
    },
    {
        question: "strawberry",
        answer: "une fraise",
        categColor: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "cherry",
        answer: "une cerise",
        categColor: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "pineapple",
        answer: "un ananas",
        categColor: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "milk",
        answer: "le lait",
        categColor: "brown"
    },
    {
        question: "tea",
        answer: "le thé",
        categColor: "dark-green"

    },
    {
        question: "cake",
        answer: "un gâteau",
        categColor: "gray"
    },
    {
        question: "hot-chocolate",
        answer: "un chocolat",
        categColor: "brown"
    },
    {
        question: "pie",
        answer: "une tarte",
        categColor: "gray"
    },
    {
        question: "ice-cream",
        answer: "une glace",
        categColor: "brown"
    },
    {
        question: "butter",
        answer: "le beurre",
        categColor: "brown"
    },
    {
        question: "bread",
        answer: "le pain",
        categColor: "gray"
    },
    {
        question: "cheese",
        answer: "le fromage",
        categColor: "brown"
    },
    {
        question: "egg",
        answer: "un oeuf",
        categColor: "orange"
    }
]